Doc of the Dead is a documentary, horror film directed by Alexandre O. Philippe.
The definitive zombie culture documentary, brought to the
screen by the makers of THE PEOPLE vs.
GEORGE LUCAS.
Self, played by Alex Cox.
Self, played by Simon Pegg.
Self, played by Bruce Campbell.
Self, played by Fran Kranz.
Self, played by George A. Romero.
Self, played by Tom Savini.
Doc of the Dead is a 2014 American documentary film
written and directed by Alexandre O.
Philippe that focuses on the zombie genre.
The film had its world premiere on March 10, 2014, at South by Southwest,
followed by a television premiere on Epix on March 15.
It features several entertainers that have had an impact on, and
been affected by, the zombie genre and culture.
The tone is dark.